night. You know, the uh that two-point
conversion the I'm sure you saw it or
heard about it.
>> I haven't seen I heard I haven't seen
it, though.
>> I just want to know if
>> there's a lateral, right? Teaching point
to you know, play through the whistle if
you mention it to players today. If
there's
>> uh it it'll be something I know that uh
Mule had already hit me about it this
morning. So, it'll be something that we
uh you know that we hit on, but I have
not seen the play yet.
>> Uh Graham made it through that
walkthrough on Wednesday, showed up in
the injury report Thursday. um what what
does that status look like? And uh given
um Tristan's also dealing with a wrist
injury, what what does the center
situation look like if Graham can't go?
>> Uh yeah, well, it's a good question. I
mean, we'll see. We've we've uh you
know, obviously worked Cologne cuz he's
he's been there. I know he's got the
wrist, but he was out there uh working
with it yesterday. uh just trying to get
Graham off his feet, you know, and uh um
but I mean, we've we've worked uh Nice,
we've worked uh Kingsley, we we've kind
of just hit all around and we we're
rolling the guards, too. So, it's really
been a little bit of a revolving door
trying to get a number of guys ready
because there's a lot of flex going into
this game right now.
>> You expect Graham to practice today?
>> Say it again. I did not see Graham Pra
today.
>> Um, what about uh Christian? Uh, does he
look like he has a chance to play on
Sunday?
>> Uh, I'll know more today. I'll know more
today. Yesterday, um, I thought he
looked pretty good. Um,
wasn't perfect, but I I thought he
looked pretty good. Um, you know, and
some of it's going to be, you know, I
know he's a little sore today. Um, and
how he feels in today's practice, you
know. Um, that's that's what a lot of
it's going to come down to.
>> You you talked a little bit about the
Steelers. I know you've said this
before, just how much you respect you
have for that organization. Tomlin was
on this run of, you know, 18 19 straight
years of no losing records. How much can
you appreciate what he's done over there
and the [clears throat] success that
he's had without any any drop?
>> Yeah, I mean, it's special. You don't I
mean, he's the work speaks for itself. I
mean, the the number of of winning
seasons that they've had and competitive
uh teams that he's had and the nature of
the way they play football, the brand of
football year after year after year is
uh I mean, it's it's rare, you know, and
in that division, by the way. I mean,
that that division has been so tough for
a for a number of years. Um, so I I just
think it's, you know, he is he's a
special coach, man. He's he's one of
these rare guys that he's got it and uh
he's been able to do it for a long
period of time.
>> Talk about the outside corners a lot
this week. We haven't talked about DK
Moff much. Just the challenges he
presents just to get out of this string
of tough passing returns.
>> Well, he he's very good as we know. He's
physical, you know, he's a big physical
man and he gets the ball in his hands.
Uh and if he gets a couple of steps, you
know, he's still got the home run speed
as we know. So, um, it's it's
interesting cuz he's he's even a little
different than some of these guys we've
faced, right? You know, I mean, Dallas,
CD, and and, uh, and George over there,
and then what we see with Nua and, and
now him, he's really different than
those guys, too, uh, in that regard. So,
you, you know, you got to be careful cuz
at any minute, he can go right down your
midline and knock you about 10 yards
deep and then he's off on his route. So,
you know, you got to prepare, you got to
challenge. I know that you can't just uh
give off soft coverage on this guy. Um
but but you know you the fight's on. I
mean this guy is he's a physical
receiver.
>> And how about Darnell Washington? You
ever seen a tight end built quite like
him? And how much does that
>> since I played
these guys existed anymore?
>> Yeah, he's you know he he is he's he's
uh you don't see guys like him anymore.
He's a big man. Uh he looks like a power
forward. Um, you know, he's big, he's
long, he's lean, but when I say lean,
you know, we know he's about 300 pounds.
I mean, so it's it's uh I mean, he's a
load. And uh you can see his length,
man. He engulfs guys in the run game and
then just his the range that he's got
from his length on the seams and
catching the ball and run after catch,
the stiff arm, the running over guys. I
mean, he's um you know, he is he's a
load. He he's a different style of
player that that there is in this league
right now.
>> Yeah. you know, here for someone like
that with such a unique size and speed.
Like, how do you just prepare during the
week for something like that?
>> Um,
well, it's it's difficult, you know,
without being able to to really, you
know, pad up and and just get out there
and have somebody run over you. You
know, we could we could put pads back on
soil and just throw it to him, let him
run over you a few times. Um, it it's
difficult. I mean, you um look, our guys
have banked a number of reps and I mean,
at this point in the season, they
there's, you know, Jack has tackled
somebody 143 times or whatever it is.
You guys could tell me that. Now, it is
different. He is bigger, but I know
this, it always starts with the first
guy. You got to get this guy wrapped up.
Grab something and then we need
population of football, man. Your
teammates are coming. And that that's
really what it is. You know, Rock, grab
grab a grab a calf, you know, Meek, you
guys get over there, get a ball out, and
teammates are coming. And that that is
the biggest help we can get as
population of football.
>> Dan, what has been the some
[clears throat] of the biggest
challenges just from a coaching
perspective about a stretch like this
where you know you you've done a lot of
really good things but still find
yourselves on the outside looking in.
>> Yeah. Well, I I think it's the as we all
know it's the inconsistencies of some of
the things
um you know that we've had that's
frustrating. It it's you never want to
lose, but when you feel like there's
things that you've done to yourself,
that's where it gets real frustrating,
you know. Um cuz we know it's hard
enough to win in this league against the
opponents, these real good opponents,
you know, but when when you feel like
sometimes you're fighting yourself a
little bit. Uh that that is very that
can be very frustrating. And so we've
had a little bit of that. Um, you know,
there's a number of circumstances, but I
I think that what I always go back to
is, man, there there's a million ways to
get the point across and to teach. And
just because it hadn't hit yet, I mean,
you just you keep going through them,
man. Go find something else. Keep
working on something else. There's
always another drill that you haven't
done before. There's always another way
to say it that finally hits somebody.
And that's what I'm always I keep my
hope in, you know, cuz I know what
that's like sitting in those seats. I I
know what it's like to be a coach. Um,
and so I've seen it from all
perspectives and uh, and you just keep
working till you get yourself out of it.
>> This group stems from the experience
gained down the stretch each of the last
three years.
>> Yeah, a lot. You know, I go back to the
the the group, the core of this team has
been through a lot. You know, they've
been through a lot. They've been through
it together, too. Uh, which is where
we've been fortunate. Most of the
coaches have, not all of them, but um,
so, you know, I mean, I
just just the work yesterday. This is
why I love these guys because they
don't,
you know, we we just like every team, we
chart everything. You mark everything,
you chart everything. You see their
speeds, you see their uh you know, the
change of direction, the all of it. Um
deceleration, right? And I mean, it was
some of the best we've had all year, you
know? I mean, it's up there. And so,
it's just proves the point. Like, our
guys go back to work, man. They don't
they don't worry about it. They don't
sulk about it. They know that they got
to clean it up. They want to win as bad
as anybody does, right? They're the ones
out there on the field. So, um, you just
give them something you feel like they
can win with. They take a hold of it and
then they bring it to life. Um, so we
got the right guys.
>> The league is always cyclical
schematically. Um, seems like it's
moving back, I guess, a little bit more
old school. the running game is
re-emphasized with some of the top backs
getting paid the way they are. We're
seeing these 13 personnel teams coming
through. I know you guys have been doing
that stuff for a while. Um, one, how
much do you kind of enjoy that the
league is trending that way? And then
two, in terms of copycat, matching it,
staying ahead of the curve. What What's
the balance there when you get to the
offseason? Do you do you always try to
guess what's next and and be ahead of
it, or are you trying to just match what
the league is doing?
>> Yeah. Well, I think you always got, you
know, your own philosophy, what you
believe in. Um, you can never go too far
away from that, but I think we'll just
go to the spread offense next year.
That's what we're going to do. We're
going four wides and have our
quarterback and we're we're good. So,
>> your alley,
>> you asked me that today. So, you know,
no, we we uh you keep up with all that
stuff. you know, I'm I'm always going to
be there's things I believe in and
principles, but um you know, but there's
always different ways to to dress it up
a little bit, you know, and uh so I
think you always have to evolve and and
find a better way to do it and um and
and try to keep defenses on their heels
a little bit.
>> Dan Jameson is closing in on career
highs and receptions, yards, and TDs.
came up yesterday when we were speaking
to him. He kind of brushed it off, just
said he's just doing his job. But it's
somebody that's been invested in his
growth from year to year. How pleased
are what you seeing from him this
season?
>> Yeah, I mean, I'm proud of I'm proud of
him. Just and it's it's all him. The
amount of work he's put in and the
amount of stuff that he's gone through,
how wherever it came, you know, how it
came, whether it was outside or it was
his own doing, whatever the case is,
man, he overcame all of it. and he's and
he just continues to, you know, he's
grown so much and uh I mean, he's a vet,
man. He's a vet. He's a pro. The way he
works, the way he he uh digests the game
plan, uh what it means to him, uh he
loves to compete. He wants to win, and
he's just taking off. And man, his
details are getting better. when you got
the uh you know the athletic ability he
has and and now the other things begin
to come and the discipline of of your
route depth and the width and and how
you stop and where you come back to the
quarterback, what golf wants, what we're
looking for, all these things. I mean,
that first dagger he caught on third
down where he got his width back on it,
I don't even know, you know, I mean,
that was that's big time. That's huge.
Uh because now G can anticipate it and
let it go before the rush gets to him.
well before he's even getting into the
break cuz now he knows he he knows that
he's got the width to drop it in the
window and with his speed and ability to
stop it makes it very difficult. So he's
grown a ton. I'm proud of himself.
>> Yeah.
[music]
>> [music]